<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hugo Bootstrap v4 Blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hugo Bootstrap v4 Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>Except where otherwise noted, content on this site is licensed under a [Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International license](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/).[备案号](http://www.com)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/2014/09/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/09/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/2014/03/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/03/migrate-to-hugo-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/2014/04/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/04/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/2014/04/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/04/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/1/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/</guid>
      <description>科学技术协会第一次培训
2022年10月9日，为了提高信工学院学生的科学技术和探索钻研的能力，信息工程学院科学技术协会于下午6：30借助钉钉平台进行直播授课，本次授课的主讲人为戚亚雄学长、闫霖学长、刘知达学长。
本次的培训内容分为三部分：ps软件的使`python的安装和技术的讲解以及unity的安装。
培训中，戚亚雄学长首先为我们讲解了ps技术的优点，并且，趁着国庆浓厚的爱国氛围，戚亚雄学长特意教授了我们国旗头像的制作，同学们积极参与，求知若渴，戚亚雄学长也非常耐心的讲解了过程，对有疑问的同学细心指导，为同学们探索ps的世界打开了一扇大门。
之后，闫霖学长也向我们分享了python技术的学习经验和python在生活中的实际应用。在这堂课上，闫霖学长细心讲解了python的安装教程，并推荐了一些关于python学习的视频，这对同学们进一步了解python有很大的帮助。在这堂课的最后，闫霖学长还为我们展示了他自己打代码做出来的小游戏，这极大激发了同学们学习python的兴趣。
经过两轮教学，同学们的学习兴趣依然热烈。短暂休息过后，刘知达学长也开始了视效媒体的授课，由于同学们刚接触视效媒体，刘知达学长在这节课只指导了同学们安装unity并讲述了视效媒体的运用，比如3D建模，动漫剪辑等等，同学们对此都很感兴趣，并与学长积极互动。
本次培训在同学们援疑质理和学长的耳提面命中很快过去，虽然每堂课的时间有限，但同学们都有所收获。学习新知识固然困难，但只要同学们带着满腔热情与一往无前的勇气，知识终将牢牢掌握在我们的手掌之中。“世上无难事，只要肯登攀”同学们应当争做上九天揽月，下五洋捉鳖的新青年！
科学技术协会
2022年10月9日</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
